Office of the Associate Vice-President, Academic fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Senate committee records, 1984 - 1998; F-201-5; 1.32 m of textual records
  - Senate Committee on Academic Planning (SCAP), 1990 - 1994; F-201-5-5; 33 cm of textual records; Senate Committee on University Priorities
    - Senate Committee on Academic Planning (SCAP), vol. 1, 1994; F-201-5-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 201-65)
    - Senate Committee on Academic Planning (SCAP), vol. 2, 1994; F-201-5-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 201-65)
    - Senate Committee on Academic Planning (SCAP), vol. 3, 1994; F-201-5-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 201-65)
    - Senate Committee on Academic Planning (SCAP), vol. 4, 1994; F-201-5-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 201-66)
    - Senate Committee on Academic Planning (SCAP), vol. 5, 1994; F-201-5-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 201-66)
    - Senate Committee on Academic Planning (SCAP), vol. 6, 1994; F-201-5-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 201-66)
  - Senate Undergraduate Awards Adjudications Committee (SUAAC), 1990 - 1995; F-201-5-6; 4 cm of textual records; Senate Undergraduate Awards Adjudication Committee
    The Senate Undergraduate Awards Adjudication Committee (SUAAC) was established in 1986 when the former Senate Committee on Scholarships, Bursaries and Awards (SCSAB) was replaced by three separate committees with distinct responsibilities for policy, undergraduate adjudication, and graduate adjudication. The main functions of SUAAC are to adjudicate all undergraduate private and university awards; recommend changes or additions to the award programs; interview students in order to prepare recommendations where required for external agencies; confer with scholarship students; and present scholarships at secondary school convocations, as required.
    This sub-series consists of the Associate Vice-President, Academic's working files as Chair of SUAAC. Records include agendas, minutes, correspondence, reports, award nominations and lists of recipients.
    Senate Undergraduate Awards Adjudication Committee
    - Senate Undergraduate Awards Adjudication Committee (SUAAC), 1990 - 1993; F-201-5-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 201-66)
      Creator's original file classification code: 5.E.
    - Senate Undergraduate Awards Adjudication Committee (SUAAC), 1994 - 1995; F-201-5-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 201-66)
      Creator's original file classification code: 4.C.b.
  - Senate Committee on Enrolment Management and Planning (SCEMP), 1992 - 1998; F-201-5-7; 6 cm of textual records; Senate Committee on Enrolment Management and Planning
    The Senate Committee on Enrolment Management and Planning (SCEMP) is a standing committee of Senate, established in 1989. Its functions are to make recommendations to Senate relating to enrolment targets, monitor the impact of enrolment limitation measures, and develop and recommend policies for managing enrolment.
    This sub-series consists of the Associate Vice-President, Academic's working files as a member of SCEMP. Records include agendas, minutes, correspondence, reports and statistics.
    - Senate Committee on Enrolment Management and Planning (SCEMP), 1992 - 1993; F-201-5-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 201-66)
    - Senate Committee on Enrolment Management and Planning (SCEMP), 1993 - 1994; F-201-5-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 201-67)
    - Senate Committee on Enrolment Management and Planning (SCEMP), 1995 - 1998; F-201-5-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 201-67)
  - Senate Committee to Review Academic Discipline and Student Conduct Policies (SCRAD), 1993 - 1994; F-201-5-8; 8 cm of textual records; Senate Committee to Review Academic Discipline and Student Conduct Policies
    The Senate Committee to Review Academic Discipline and Student Conduct Policies (SCRAD) was an ad hoc committee established by Senate in May 1993 to review university academic discipline and student conduct policies. SCRAD reported to Senate in 1994. As an outcome of its recommendations, the university adopted a package of policies and procedures relating to student discipline, dissolved the former Senate Committee on Academic Discipline (SCAD), and replaced it with two new bodies, the University Board of Student Discipline (UBSD) and the Senate Committee on Disciplinary Appeals (SCODA).
    This sub-series consists of the Associate Vice-President, Academic's working files as Chair of SCRAD. Records include agendas, minutes, correspondence, reports, policies, drafts, notes, and working papers.
    - Senate Ad Hoc Committee to Review Academic Discipline and Student Conduct Policies (SCRAD), vol. 1, 1993 - 1994; F-201-5-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 201-67)
    - Senate Ad Hoc Committee to Review Academic Discipline and Student Conduct Policies (SCRAD), vol. 2, 1993 - 1994; F-201-5-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 201-67)
    - Senate Ad Hoc Committee to Review Academic Discipline and Student Conduct Policies (SCRAD), vol. 3, 1993 - 1994; F-201-5-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 201-67)
    - Senate Ad Hoc Committee to Review Academic Discipline and Student Conduct Policies (SCRAD), vol. 4, 1993 - 1994; F-201-5-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 201-67)
  - Senate Committee on Course Scheduling (SCCS), 1995 - 1996; F-201-5-9; 5 cm of textual records; Senate Committee on Course Scheduling and Timetabling
    The Senate Committee on Course Scheduling and Timetabling (SCCS) was an ad hoc committee created by Senate in October 1995 to review the scheduing and timetabling of undergraduate courses and consider whether formal policies and procedures were required. SCCS reported back to Senate in May 1996.
    This sub-series consists of the Associate Vice-President, Academic's working files as a member of SCCS. Records include correspondence, reports, statistics, notes, and working papers.
    - Sebate Committee on Course Scheduling (SCCS), vol. 1, 1995 - 1996; F-201-5-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 201-68)
    - Sebate Committee on Course Scheduling (SCCS), vol. 2, 1995 - 1996; F-201-5-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 201-68)
    - Sebate Committee on Course Scheduling (SCCS), vol. 3, 1995 - 1996; F-201-5-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 201-68)